officers so earlier I don't know if you I don't know who called you uh-huh but there was a couple
of people rescuing a bird that was injured clearly in distress and not in I think lawful regulations
okay and uh this this fellow over here and a few other fellows were all physically putting their
hands under I have all the footage here okay I don't know if you guys would want to review that
and see but they were like physically assaulting her physically assaulting the person or the bird
the person holding the bird uh you know who it was so the main guy I believe that you talked to
that's got gray hair yeah he's one of the few gray-haired guys yeah uh he was one of them he
was the one that was assaulting the other person yeah I have footage of it I mean the thing is like
the person that got assaulted never called so it's like we don't really have a complaint okay so even
if you call like if I could find her I'm here independently as a journalist but okay so if you
could find her and she wants to make a complaint then you could just be with her and call 911 and then
from there they'll come and they'll make a report you could also go to the precinct because you're here
right yeah you could also go to the precinct well you could show them the footage right you know then and
they'll have to review it and if you want them uh you can send it over to them too they could just like
take it off the flash drive right then and there too okay yeah okay is it a certain precinct local
so the 9-0 precinct is the local precinct that covers this okay so we don't yeah we don't work there we're
just here to like you know make sure nobody gets into a fight whatever or like any anything along those
lines yeah because they used to get very like so that's what we found out that uh in the recent times
like beforehand they used like they used to get very violent they used to fight with each other
not the people that are celebrating but the people that used to come and protest and have an issue with
the way whatever they're doing we're just here to make sure that nobody fights or nobody does anything
because I guess the government allows them to do do this they have an issue that it's against the
mental hygiene law and everything so it's just a back and forth but this year has been very calm
according to everyone else that came in we had a lady from the mayor's office just now here she was
speaking to us so she's the one that informed me because I I never worked here this is my first year
working in Brooklyn I used to work in Harlem before this so I never was the lady from the mayor's office
informing you was she informing you about the assault or was she no she was informing me about like how in
recent times like about last year the year before that like when they used to do the celebration they used to
get very violent yeah like people used to fight each other whatever whatever but this year has been very calm and
nothing like that happened are there any discussions within the police or the government about the hygiene
side of it or the side of what these activists are protesting against honestly I have no idea like if I
dead I would tell you but I don't I don't okay yeah you don't know anything about that I don't know
anything about that this is our first time doing this so no one so they told us what the tradition is they
they never said anything about the laws or say um even then that's just all like coming from higher up
yeah they're the ones that are going to be like oh you know they can't do this yeah like can't do this if that was the case they would
tell us what they can't tell us if they didn't tell us anything that means they're allowing this did they say
they're preparing you for this like if there is a bird physically like in distress like some of them
are dehydrated they've got lacerations they're bleeding out stuff like that did they give you
any kind of instructions instructions on that no we didn't give them instructions okay
by the way I'm not trying to give a gotcha you guys I'm not going to try to get you guys in trouble
I just think this thing's weird as hell and I'm trying to understand listen everybody has their own views
yeah I'm in my uniform I can't say much yeah I understand so I'm just here to do my job right yeah
they told me to stay here make sure nobody gets into any crazy altercation or whatever and yeah
that's what we're trying I believe in religious freedom you know correct it's like to what extent
you know like this is out on the side of the road anyways I know you're not I mean you can't say
anything I'm not you know try to make you say something on I know okay well appreciate it I'll I'll try
to check out the 90 and see it because it really was so it's it's the night it's the nine oh yeah and then
for you to file that complaint you need that CV with you so basically if you don't have a
complainant like you're just filing a report for no reason you understand yeah if the complaint is
not filing a report you never got assaulted like you're just a third-party caller yeah saying like
I seen somebody get assaulted whatever but if they don't have an issue with it then okay it's not
much I'll see if I can find her and if she wants help that's all all right I felt bad for her she was a
girl by herself oh you know yeah I'm sorry to hear that but okay all right take care
all right no problem appreciate you